I will go on a walk.
我要去散步
I must wear warm things.
我必须穿上暖和的东西
I walk and walk in the snow.
我在雪里走啊走
I hike up this tall, tall rock.
我爬上这块高高的石头
I stop, sit, and look as far as I can.
我停下来   坐下   极目远眺
From here I can spot a seal.
从这里我能发现一只海豹
It is big, and its skin shines.
它很大   它的皮肤在发光
It looks at me.
它看着我
From here I can spot the whales.
从这里我能发现鲸鱼们
The whales swim in the water.
鲸鱼们在水里游泳
They look at me.
它们看着我
From this rock I can spot the birds.
从这块石头这里我能发现鸟儿们
The birds look up.
鸟儿们向上看
They all look at me.
它们都看着我
I can see the penguins.
我能看到企鹅们
They walk tall.
他们昂首挺胸
They all call and call.
它们都叫啊叫
I call to them all,
我对它们喊
"I like this place of ice, and I like all of you!"
我喜欢这个冰天雪地的地方   我喜欢你们